Guide to the Cornell University College of Engineering Alumni Affairs and Development Office records, 1959-1992.
Cornell University College of Engineering Alumni Affairs and Development Office records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University College of Engineering Alumni Affairs and Development Office records, 1959-1992.
16-17-3405
Cornell University. College of Engineering.
.4 cubic ft.
Photographs, memorabilia, and printed materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes files and photographs of the dedication of various engineering labs and buildings and the 125th anniversary symposium.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes files and photographs of the dedication of various engineering labs and buildings and the 125th anniversary symposium.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University. College of Engineering -- Buildings.; Cornell University. College of Engineering
Subjects:
Buildings
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Events
  - Special Dean's Visit, August 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 125th Anniversary, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Awards process, May 22, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - World War II era Reunion, April 1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Group Photo, June 4, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Homecoming Photos, October 10, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Development Directors' Conference Photo, April 12, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - De Frees Lab Groundbreaking - memos and photos., 1983-1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - De Frees Lab Dedication, 1983-1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Holbrook Dedication, September 1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Meinig Dedication, June 1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Takeo Mogami Geotechnical Lab Dedication, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Olin Hall Dedication, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Sage Hall Dedication, October 2, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Snee Hall Dedication, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Engineering Theory Center Dedication, June 5, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 16-18)
  - Upson Hall Dedication, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)